noodles.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy - Noodles & Company

**Noodles & Company Privacy Policy**

**Last Updated**

Privacy Policy last updated on October 12, 2016.

At Noodles & Company (“Noodles”, “we”, or “us”), we understand your privacy is important to you and we want to let you know the kinds of information we may gather, why we gather your information, what we use your information for, when we might disclose your information, and how you can manage your information. This Privacy Policy is applicable to Noodles’ website located at [www.noodles.com](http://www.noodles.com/), applications and online services that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Site”).  This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may submit to us offline, or to third-party websites and mobile applications that may be linked to or from the Site. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of these third-party websites and applications.

**By using our Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. We may modify the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. Your continued use of our Sites following the posting of changes will mean you accept those changes.**

**_Information We Collect_**

We collect personal information about you, meaning information that can uniquely identify you, directly from you when you use the Site, such as when you register for an account, join our rewards program, or access certain features or content. The personal information we collect about you includes

  * contact information, such as your name and email address;
  * ordering information, such as your street address and phone number;
  * your birthday if you are a member of our rewards program;
  * demographic information, such as your state and country of residence; and
  * login information, such as your username and password.

**Collection of Information from Social Media Sites and other Sources**

When you interact with any Noodles page or account on a social media platform, we may collect information you make available to us on that page, including your account ID or username. If you choose to log in to your Noodles account with or through a social networking service, Noodles and that service may share certain information about you and your activities. With your permission, we also may share information about your activities, including what you view on the Sites, with that social network’s users.

We also may collect information about you that we may receive from other sources or from our offline interactions with you to help us verify and update information contained in our records and to better customize the Site for you.

**Non-Personal Information We Collect**

We also collect information when users interact with the Site. This information does not personally identify you. Generally, we collect and store the following types of information:

  * demographic data such as age, gender, and ZIP code;
  * device information about devices used to access the Site; and
  * usage and traffic information such as pages viewed on the Site, the date and time of access, and referring website addresses.

**Collection of Your Location Information**

You may send us information which may disclose your general location at the time you access the Site. Advertisements and certain content may be directed to you as a result of the collection of this data. In addition, in some cases the Site can deliver content based on your specific location if you choose to enable that feature.

**Use of Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Technologies**

Like most websites, we may use “cookies”, which are small text files that are stored on your computer or equipment when you visit certain online pages that record your preferences and actions. We use cookies to track use of our Site and exposure to our online advertisements.

We may also use cookies to monitor traffic, improve the Site, and make it easier to use and more relevant. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies but, if you prefer, you can usually modify your browser setting to disable or reject cookies. If you delete your cookies or if you set your browser to decline cookies, some features of the Sites may not work or may not work as designed. For more information on cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

We may also use web beacons or other technologies to help us better understand how users use our Site, to customize the Site and provide our users a better Site experience. A web beacon is an invisible graphic on a web page that is programmed to collect non identifiable information about your use of the website.

The Site also uses Google Analytics which uses cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with and use the Site, compile reports on Site activity, and provides other services related to Site activity and usage. Google Analytics may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, and referring website. The Site does not use Google Analytics to gather personal information. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s privacy policies.

Some applications and functionality on the Site are provided by third parties. We may enable third parties to collect information in connection with our website.  This privacy policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, any collection of information by third parties on our website.

We may also use third party service providers to assist us in providing certain functionality on our Site. For example, when you place an order online, our service provider accepts and submits the order to us, and also processes your payment. We have agreements with our services providers to protect your information, however, their practices may vary from ours.  Please review their terms of service and privacy policies before you provide any information to those service providers.  If you have any questions about our service providers’ practices, please either contact the service provider directly, or let us know and we will help get your questions answered.

**_How We Use Your Information_**

We use your information to help us personalize and continually improve your experience on the Site. We may use your personal and non-personal information in the following ways:

  * to provide you with the content, products and services you request;
  * to communicate with you about your account or transactions with us and send you information about features and enhancements on or to our Site,
  * to communicate with you about changes to our policies,
  * to send you newsletters, offers, promotions, or other communications about our products and services, including special or promotional events;
  * to advertise our products and services;
  * to administer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, and surveys;
  * to administer loyalty and rewards programs;
  * to detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal;
  * to improve our menu offerings and operations; and
  * to perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses.

We may use your information collected on one portion of the Site with information collected on other portions of the Site, and we may combine that information into a single record. We may also use or combine information that we collect offline or we collect or receive from third-party sources to enhance, expand, and verify our records.

We may disclose your non-personal information in any other manner that we deem appropriate. Among other things, way disclose non-personal information to third parties to help us determine how people use the Site and how we can improve our Site. We will also disclose non-personal information to our service providers and other third parties about how our users collectively use the Site.

**_How We Share Your Information  _**

We may share your information with our service providers, affiliates, partners, and other third parties as described below.

**Third-Party Service Providers**

We have third-party service providers, agents, franchisees, subsidiaries, and affiliates that perform functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to: hosting, content syndication, content management, technical integration, marketing, analytics, customer service, and fraud protection.

These entities may have access to your information if needed to perform their services or functions. If such access is required, the third parties will be contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of your personal information. The service providers are restricted from using, selling, or distributing this information in any way other than to provide the requested services to the Site.

**Assignment**

We may change our ownership or corporate organization while providing the Site. We may also sell certain assets associated with the Site. In such event, we may transfer some or all of your information to an entity acquiring all or part of our assets or to another entity with which we have merged. Under such circumstances, we would request the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Nevertheless, we cannot promise that an acquiring party or the merged entity will have the same privacy practices or treat your information the same as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Law Enforcement, Legal Process, and Emergency Situations**

We may also use or disclose PII if required to do so by law or on the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal requirements; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, the Sites or our users, or (c) act to protect the personal safety of us, users of the Sites or the public.

**_How We Protect Your Information_**

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect your information. We may request proof of identity before we disclose your information to you. While we try our best to safeguard your information when we have it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network is 100% secure.

**_Storing Your Information_**

The time period for which we keep your information varies according to what the information is used for. In some cases, there are legal requirements to keep data for a minimum period. Unless there is a specific legal requirement for us to keep the information, we will retain it for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the data was collected or for which it is to be further used. ** **

**_Children’s Information_**

The Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. Noodles does not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, do not provide personal information to Noodles. If you are between 13 and 18 years of age, do not provide personal information to Noodles without a parent or guardian’s consent.

If we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information and we do not have parental consent, we will promptly delete that child’s information from the Site. If you believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Noodles with personal information without parental consent, please notify us immediately at 720-214-1900.

**_Public Areas of the Site_**

Any information you share in public areas of the Site becomes public and anyone may see your posts. Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any private or sensitive information. Noodles does not control who views information that you post in public areas and is not responsible for how third parties may use or disclose information that you post in public areas.

**_Contests and Promotions_**

When we run a contest, sweepstakes or other promotion on our Site, there will be specific rules that apply to the promotion that will explain how the information you provide in order to participate will be used and disclosed.

**_Notice to Users Outside the United States_**

The Site is located and directed to individuals in the United States.  If you are accessing the Site from outside the U.S., you do so at your sole risk and are responsible for compliance with all applicable local laws.

If you choose to use the Site outside of the United States, you understand and consent to the transfer of your personal information to, and the collection, processing and storage of your personal information in, the United States and other countries. The laws in the U.S. regarding personal information may be different than the laws of your state or country.

If you have an account with Noodles on or through the Site, you may review and change your information by logging into your account and editing your profile, via email by contacting us at [guestrelations@noodles.com](mailto:guestrelations@noodles.com) by calling 720-214-1900, or Need Help within the app. Please note that we may not be able to delete your personal information without also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change or delete your personal information if we believe doing so would violate any law or legal requirement, or cause the information to be incorrect.

You may opt-out of receiving future e-mail marketing messages and e-mail newsletters from Noodles at any time, by using the “unsubscribe” link found on each of our email communications.

**_Changes to our Privacy Policy_**

From time to time, we may update this Privacy Policy. If our information practices materially change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our Site to notify you of these changes, and we will only use data collected from the time of the policy change forward for these new or different purposes. In the event we make a material change to how we use your personal information, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of such new or different use. The date this Privacy Notice was last revised is at the top of this page. You are responsible for periodically reviewing the Site and this Privacy Policy to check for any updates or changes.

**_Information for our California Website Visitors.   _**

Your web browser may let you choose your preference as to whether you want to allow websites to collect personal information over time about your online activities across different websites or online services.  At this time our website does not respond to the preferences you may have set in your web browser regarding the collection of your information, and our website may continue to collect information in the manner described in this privacy policy.

If you are a California resident and customer of Noodles, you have the right to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [guestrelations@noodles.com](mailto:guestrelations@noodles.com) or write us at: Noodles & Company, attn.: 520 Zang Street, Broomfield, CO 80021.

Copyright © 2016 NOODLES & Company. All rights reserved.
